<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feature
      id="com.tibco.cep.studio.streambase.feature"
      label="StreamBase SDK Feature"
      version="5.6.1"
      provider-name="TIBCO Software Inc.">

   <description url="http://www.tibco.com/products/event-processing/">
      Shared TIBCO SDK providing Decision Table designtime functionality.
   </description>

   <license url="license.html">
      STREAMBASE TRIAL KIT
DEVELOPMENT LICENSE AGREEMENT

BY INDICATING YOUR ACCEPTANCE BELOW OR BY DOWNLOADING, 
INSTALLING OR USING THE STREAMBASE SOFTWARE 
LICENSED HEREUNDER (THE &quot;SOFTWARE&quot;), YOU 
(TOGETHER WITH THE BUSINESS OR OTHER ENTITY 
FOR WHICH THE SOFTWARE IS OBTAINED, &quot;YOU&quot; 
OR &quot;LICENSEE&quot;) ARE CONSENTING TO BE BOUND BY 
AND ARE BECOMING A PARTY TO THIS STREAMBASE 
TRIAL KIT DEVELOPMENT LICENSE AGREEMENT 
(&quot;AGREEMENT&quot;) WITH STREAMBASE SYSTEMS, INC. 
(&quot;STREAMBASE&quot;). IF YOU ARE NOT AN EMPLOYEE OF 
THE LICENSEE, OR IF YOU ARE NOT OTHERWISE 
AUTHORIZED TO ENTER INTO THIS AGREEMENT OR IF 
YOU DO NOT AGREE TO ALL OF THE TERMS OF THIS 
AGREEMENT, DO NOT ACCEPT AND CANCEL THIS INSTALLER. IF THESE TERMS 
ARE CONSIDERED AN OFFER, ACCEPTANCE IS EXPRESSLY 
LIMITED TO THESE TERMS. PLEASE PRINT A COPY OF 
THIS AGREEMENT FOR YOUR FUTURE REFERENCE IF YOU 
DECIDE TO ACCEPT.

License

Subject to the terms and conditions of this Agreement 
and any documentation, StreamBase hereby grants to 
Licensee a nonexclusive, nontransferable limited 
license on a trial basis solely for the Term of this 
Agreement (as defined below) for a single user to use 
the Software (in object code format) on a single 
computer only for the purpose of developing a 
prototype of Licensee&apos;s application for Licensee&apos;s 
internal evaluation and non-commercial purposes, and 
not for any other purpose. If Licensee uses the 
application developed under this license for any 
internal data processing or for any commercial or 
production purposes, or wants to use the Software for 
any purpose other than as permitted under this 
Agreement, Licensee must contact StreamBase to obtain 
the appropriate license.

Ownership and Restrictions

StreamBase retains all ownership and intellectual 
property rights in the Software, including any 
generated code. The Software may be installed on one 
computer only, and used by one person in the operating 
environment identified by StreamBase. Licensee may 
make one copy of the software solely for backup 
purposes.

You may not:
* use the Software for your own internal data processing 
  or for any commercial or production purposes, or use 
  the Software for any purpose except the development of 
  a prototype of your application;
* use the application you develop with the Software for 
  any internal data processing or commercial or 
  production purposes without securing an appropriate 
  license from StreamBase; 
* continue to develop your application after you have 
  used it for any internal data processing, commercial 
  or production purpose without securing an appropriate 
  license from StreamBase;
* remove or modify any software markings or any notice 
  of StreamBase&apos;s proprietary rights;
* make the Software available in any manner to any 
  third party;
* use the Software to provide third party training;
* assign this Agreement or give or transfer the Software 
  or any interest in it to any third party;
* cause or permit modification, reverse engineering, 
  disassembly or decompilation of the Software; 
* use any means to obtain, access or examine any source 
  or class files of the Software (with the exception of 
  source code generated by provided code template wizards
  in Studio and other tools provided with the software);
* modify or create derivative works of the Software;
* perform any Software benchmark and/or performance 
  tests (or disclose results thereof) without 
  StreamBase&apos;s prior consent; or
* use any StreamBase name, trademark or logo.

Upon reasonable advance written notice, StreamBase shall 
have the right to have an independent auditor verify 
Licensee&apos;s compliance with this Agreement. Licensee 
shall make its systems and all applicable books and 
records available for such inspection during normal 
business hours at Licensee&apos;s principal place of 
business.

Licensee acquires no ownership of the Licensed Product 
from this Agreement and no right to possess or use the 
Licensed Product outside of the licenses granted herein.
All rights not expressly granted herein are reserved by 
StreamBase and its suppliers.

Term

This Agreement will remain in effect until the 
expiration date embedded in the Trial Kit license 
file sent to the Licensee by TIBCO Software Inc., 
provided that the Agreement has been accepted by 
the Licensee (the &quot;Term&quot;). Licensee may terminate this 
Agreement any time by ceasing to use the software and 
destroying all copies of the Software in its possession 
or control, including as embedded in any developer 
application. This Agreement will automatically terminate 
without notice upon any breach any term of this 
Agreement. Upon termination, Licensee shall cease 
using the Software, and delete all copies of the 
Software in your possession or control.

Disclaimer of Warranties 

Licensee understands that the Software may have errors 
and may produce unexpected results. Licensee agrees that 
any use of the Software, will be entirely at Licensee&apos;s 
own risk. Licensee agrees to back up data and take other 
appropriate measures to protect programs and data. 

THE SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED &quot;AS IS&quot; AND WITHOUT 
WARRANTY, EXPRESS OR IMPLIED. STREAMBASE AND ITS 
SUPPLIERS SPECIFICALLY DISCLAIM ANY EXPRESS OR 
IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF ANY KIND, INCLUDING 
WITHOUT LIMITATION, MERCHANTABILITY AND 
FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE.

Limitation of Liability

IN NO EVENT WILL STREAMBASE OR ITS SUPPLIERS BE 
LIABLE FOR ANY DAMAGES, INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED 
TO ANY LOST PROFITS, LOST SAVINGS OR ANY DIRECT, 
INCIDENTAL OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES, WHETHER 
RESULTING FROM IMPAIRED OR LOST DATA, SOFTWARE OR 
COMPUTER FAILURE OR ANY OTHER CAUSE, OR FOR 
AGGREGATE DAMAGES IN EXCESS OF US$100, IN EACH 
CASE, EVEN IF STREAMBASE OR ITS SUPPLIERS ARE 
ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGES, OR 
FOR ANY OTHER CLAIM BY LICENSEE OR FOR ANY THIRD 
PARTY CLAIM.

No Technical Support 

Licensee acknowledges and agrees that StreamBase will 
not provide technical support, phone support, or 
updates to Licensee for the Software licensed under 
this Agreement.

Reports

Feedback and reporting of bugs to StreamBase is 
encouraged. Please do so by sending email to 
dev-support@streambase.com. Licensee agrees that 
the contents of all oral and written reports to 
StreamBase and any other materials, information, 
ideas, concepts, and know-how provided by Licensee 
(including suggestions for improvements and corrections
to problems in the Software and documentation) become 
the property of StreamBase.

Open Source

&quot;Open Source&quot; software -- software available without 
charge for use, modification and distribution -- is 
often licensed under terms that require the user to 
make the user&apos;s modifications to the Open Source 
software or any software that the user &apos;combines&apos; 
with the Open Source software freely available in 
source code form. If you use Open Source software in 
conjunction with the Software, you must ensure that 
your use does not: (i) create, or purport to create, 
obligations of StreamBase with respect to the Software; 
or (ii) grant, or purport to grant, to any third party 
any rights to or immunities under intellectual 
property or proprietary rights in the Software. For 
example, you may not develop a software program using 
the Software and an Open Source program where such use 
results in a software file(s) that contains code from 
both the Software and the Open Source program 
(including without limitation libraries) if the Open 
Source program is licensed under a license that 
requires any &quot;modifications&quot; be made freely available. 
You also may not combine the Software with programs 
licensed under the GNU General Public License (&quot;GPL&quot;) 
in any manner that could cause, or could be 
interpreted or asserted to cause, the Software or any 
modifications thereto to become subject to the terms 
of the GPL.

Third Party Code

Some third-party code embedded or bundled with the 
Software may be licensed to you under different terms 
and conditions as set forth in the THIRDPARTY.html 
file. In addition to any terms and conditions of any 
third party license identified in the THIRDPARTY.html 
file, the disclaimer of warranty and limitation of 
liability provisions in this license shall apply to 
all code distributed as part of or bundled with the 
Software.

General Terms 

Relationship between the Parties

The relationship between the parties is that of 
licensee/licensor. Neither party will represent that it 
has any authority to assume or create any obligation, 
express or implied, on behalf of the other party, nor 
to represent the other party as agent, employee, 
franchisee, or in any other capacity. Nothing in 
this Agreement shall be construed to limit either 
party&apos;s right to independently develop or distribute 
software that is functionally similar to the other 
party&apos;s products, so long as proprietary information 
of the other party is not included in such Software.

License to Government

If any user of the Software or any documentation is an 
agency, department or other entity of the United States 
Government, the use, duplication, reproduction, 
modification, release, disclosure or transfer of the 
Software or documentation is restricted in accordance 
with FAR 12.212 for civilian agencies and DFAR 
227.7202 for military agencies. The Software is 
commercial computer software and the documentation is 
commercial computer software documentation. The use of 
the Software and documentation is further restricted 
in accordance with the terms of this Agreement.

Export

Licensee agrees that U.S. export control laws and other 
applicable export and import laws govern your use of the 
Software, including technical data. Licensee further 
agrees that neither the Software nor any direct product 
thereof will be exported, directly, or indirectly, in 
violation of these laws, or will be used for any purpose 
prohibited by these laws including, without limitation, 
nuclear, chemical, or biological weapons proliferation.

Governing Law

This Agreement shall be governed by and construed in 
accordance with the laws of the Commonwealth of 
Massachusetts, without regard to its conflicts of law 
provisions. The United Nations Convention on Contracts 
for the International Sale of Goods shall not apply to 
this Agreement. The sole jurisdiction and venue for 
actions related to this Agreement will be the state or 
federal courts located in Massachusetts having 
jurisdiction over StreamBase&apos;s principal offices, 
and both parties consent to the jurisdiction of such 
courts with respect to any such action. In any action 
or proceeding to enforce or interpret this Agreement, 
the prevailing party will be entitled to recover the 
costs and expenses (including reasonable attorneys&apos; 
fees) that it incurred in connection with such action 
or proceeding and enforcing any judgment or order 
obtained.

Relief

Each party agrees that, in the event of any breach or 
threatened breach of this Agreement, StreamBase will 
suffer irreparable damage for which it will have no 
adequate remedy at law. Accordingly, StreamBase shall 
be entitled to injunctive and other equitable remedies 
to prevent or restrain, temporarily or permanently, 
such breach or threatened breach, without the 
necessity of posting any bond or surety. Except as 
specifically provided otherwise, each right and remedy 
in this Agreement is in addition to any other right or 
remedy, at law or in equity, and the exercise of one 
right or remedy will not be deemed a waiver of any 
other right or remedy.

Entire Agreement

Licensee agrees that this Agreement is the complete 
agreement for the Software and the licenses granted 
herein, and this Agreement supersedes all prior or 
contemporaneous agreements or representations unless 
there is a signed agreement between the parties (in 
which case, the terms of such signed agreement shall 
govern and control). If any term of this Agreement 
is found to be invalid or unenforceable, the remaining 
provisions will remain effective. No changes, 
modifications, or waivers may be made to this Agreement 
unless in writing and signed by both parties. The 
failure of either party to enforce its rights under 
this Agreement at any time for any period will not be 
construed as a waiver of such rights. If any provision 
of this Agreement is determined to be illegal or 
unenforceable, that provision will be limited or 
eliminated to the minimum extent necessary so that 
this Agreement will otherwise remain in full force 
and effect and enforceable.

Contact Information

TIBCO Software Inc.
181 Spring Street
Lexington MA 02421
(c) 2004-2016 TIBCO Software Inc. All Rights Reserved.
   </license>

   <requires>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.emf.common" version="2.4.0" match="greaterOrEqual"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.emf.ecore.xmi" version="2.4.1" match="greaterOrEqual"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.emf.ecore" version="2.4.1" match="greaterOrEqual"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.core.resources" version="3.4.2" match="greaterOrEqual"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.core.runtime" version="3.4.0" match="greaterOrEqual"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.emf.edit" version="2.4.2" match="greaterOrEqual"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.ui"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.core.resources" version="3.7.101" match="greaterOrEqual"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.ui.forms" version="3.5.101" match="greaterOrEqual"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.emf.common.ui" version="2.7.0" match="greaterOrEqual"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.emf.ecore.xmi" version="2.7.0" match="greaterOrEqual"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.emf.edit.ui" version="2.7.0" match="greaterOrEqual"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.ui.workbench"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.ui.ide"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.ui.views.properties.tabbed" version="3.6.0" match="greaterOrEqual"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.core.filesystem"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.emf.ecore" version="2.4.2" match="greaterOrEqual"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.ltk.core.refactoring" version="3.4.2" match="greaterOrEqual"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.core.filesystem" version="1.2.0" match="greaterOrEqual"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.core.filebuffers" version="3.4.0" match="greaterOrEqual"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.text"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.jdt.core" version="3.4.4" match="greaterOrEqual"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.xsd"/>
      <import plugin="javax.wsdl" version="1.5.0" match="equivalent"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.jdt.apt.core" version="3.3.600" match="greaterOrEqual"/>
      <import plugin="org.apache.xerces" version="2.9.0" match="greaterOrEqual"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.osgi"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.equinox.common" version="3.5.1" match="greaterOrEqual"/>
      <import plugin="ca.odell.glazedlists" version="1.9.1" match="greaterOrEqual"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.jface.text"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.ui.console"/>
   </requires>

   <plugin
         id="com.tibco.cep.decision.table.common"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="0.0.0"
         unpack="false"/>

   <plugin
         id="com.tibco.cep.decision.table.core"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="0.0.0"
         unpack="false"/>

   <plugin
         id="com.tibco.cep.decision.table.ui"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="0.0.0"
         unpack="false"/>

   <plugin
         id="com.tibco.cep.rt"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="0.0.0"
         unpack="false"/>

   <plugin
         id="com.tibco.cep.studio.cli"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="0.0.0"
         unpack="false"/>

   <plugin
         id="com.tibco.cep.studio.common"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="0.0.0"
         unpack="false"/>

   <plugin
         id="com.tibco.cep.studio.core"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="0.0.0"
         unpack="false"/>

   <plugin
         id="com.tibco.cep.studio.mapper"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="0.0.0"
         unpack="false"/>

   <plugin
         id="com.tibco.cep.studio.util"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="0.0.0"
         unpack="false"/>

   <plugin
         id="com.tibco.cep.studio.xerces"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="0.0.0"
         fragment="true"
         unpack="false"/>

   <plugin
         id="com.tibco.cep.thirdparty"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="0.0.0"
         unpack="false"/>

   <plugin
         id="com.tibco.cep.tpcl"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="0.0.0"
         unpack="false"/>

   <plugin
         id="com.tibco.cep.tra"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="0.0.0"
         unpack="false"/>

   <plugin
         id="ca.odell.glazedlists"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="0.0.0"
         unpack="false"/>

   <plugin
         id="org.eclipse.nebula.widgets.nattable.core"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="0.0.0"
         unpack="false"/>

   <plugin
         id="org.eclipse.nebula.widgets.nattable.extension.glazedlists"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="0.0.0"
         unpack="false"/>

   <plugin
         id="com.tibco.xml.xmodel"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="0.0.0"
         unpack="false"/>

   <plugin
         id="com.tibco.xml.mappermodel.emfapi"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="0.0.0"
         unpack="false"/>

   <plugin
         id="com.tibco.xml.dictionaryapi"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="0.0.0"
         unpack="false"/>

   <plugin
         id="com.tibco.xml.mappermodel"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="0.0.0"
         unpack="false"/>

   <plugin
         id="javax.wsdl"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="0.0.0"
         unpack="false"/>

   <plugin
         id="org.eclipse.wst.wsdl"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="0.0.0"
         unpack="false"/>

</feature>
